Guide to the Actors' Equity Association Theatrical Programs WAG.257
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archive
- Series I: New York City, Regional Theatres and Touring Productions/Companies
  - Countess Maritza, Undated (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Country Girl, Undated (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Country Wife, Undated (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Cowgirls, Undated (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Cradle Snatchers, Undated (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Cradle Will Rock, Undated (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Craig's Wife, Undated (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Crazy for You, Undated (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Creation of the World and Other Business, Undated (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Creeps, Undated (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Crimes of the Heart, Undated (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Critic's Choice, Undated (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Crucible, Undated (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Crucifer of Blood, Undated (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Cuba and His Teddy Bear, Undated (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Curious Savage, Undated (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Curse of the Starving Class, Undated (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Custer, Undated (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Cymbeline, Undated (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Cyrano[the musical], Undated (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Cyrano de Bergerac, Undated (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - D, Undated (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - D, 1920s (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - D, 1930s (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - D, 1940s (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - D, 1950s (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - D, 1960s (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - D (file 1 of 2), 1970s (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - D (file 2 of 2), 1970s (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - D (file 1 of 2), 1980s (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - D (file 2 of 2), 1980s (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - D, 1990s (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - D, 2000s (Box 9, Folder 5A)
  - Da, Undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Daddy Goodness, Undated (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Dames at Sea, Undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Damien, Undated (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Damn Yankees, Undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Dance a Little Closer, Undated (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Dance of Death, Undated (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Dancin', Undated (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Dancin' in the Streets!, Undated (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Dancing at Lughnasa, Undated (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Dancing in the End Zone, Undated (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Danger: Memory, Undated (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Dangerous Games, Undated (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Danny and the Deep Blue Sea, Undated (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Danton's Death, Undated (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Dark of the Moon, Undated (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Daughters, Undated (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Day in Hollywood; A Night in the Ukraine, Undated (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Day in the Death of Joe Egg, Undated (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Dead End, Undated (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Deadly Game, Undated (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Dear Liar, Undated (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Dear Me, the Sky is Falling, Undated (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Dear World, Undated (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Death and the King's Horseman, Undated (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Death Defying Acts, Undated (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Death of a Salesman, Undated (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Death of Bessie Smith and The American Dream, Undated (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Deathtrap, Undated (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Debutante Ball, Undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Deep Are the Roots, Undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Delicate Balance, Undated (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Deputy, Undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Desert Song, Undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Design for Living, Undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Desire Under the Elms, Undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Desk Set, Undated (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Desperate Hours, Undated (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Destry Rides Again, Undated (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Detective Story, Undated (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Devils, Undated (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Devil's Advocate, Undated (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Devil's Disciple, Undated (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Devour the Snow, Undated (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Dial 'M' for Murder, Undated (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Diamond Studs, Undated (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Diary of Ann Frank, Undated (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Dining Room, Undated (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Dinner at Eight, Undated (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Dirtiest Show in Town, Undated (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Dirty Blonde, Undated (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Disenchanted, Undated (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Disintegration of James Cherry, Undated (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Diversions and Delights, Undated (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Diving Drudge, Undated (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Diviners, Undated (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Divorce Me, Darling, Undated (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Do Black Patent Leather Shoes Really Reflect Up?, Undated (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Do I Hear a Waltz?, Undated (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Do Not Go Gentle, Undated (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Do Re Mi, Undated (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Do You Know the Milky Way?, Undated (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Doctor's Dilemma, Undated (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Does a Tiger Wear a Necktie?, Undated (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Dog's Logic, Undated (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Doll's House, Undated (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Don Juan, Undated (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Don Juan in Hell, Undated (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Don't Bother Me, I Can't Cope, Undated (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Don't Dress for Dinner, Undated (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Don't Drink the Water, Undated (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Don't Play Us Cheap, Undated (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Doonesbury, Undated (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Double Feature, Undated (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Doughgirls, Undated (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Down the Road, Undated (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Downstairs Boy, Undated (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Dracula, Undated (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Drat the Cat, Undated (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - Dream Girl, Undated (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - Dream on Monkey Mountain, Undated (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - Dreamgirls, Undated (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - Dresser, Undated (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Driving Miss Daisy, Undated (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Du Barry Was a Lady, Undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Duel of Angels, Undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Duet for One, Undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Dumbwaiter and The Collection, Undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Dybbuk, Undated (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Dylan, Undated (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Dynamite Tonight, Undated (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Dynamo, Undated (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Dyson, Undated (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - E, Undated (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - E, 1915 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - E, 1920s (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - E, 1930s (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - E, 1940s (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - E, 1950s (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - E, 1960s (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - E, 1970s (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - E (file 1 of 2), 1980s (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - E (file 2 of 2), 1980s (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - E, 1990s (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - E, 2000s (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Earl Carroll "Vanities," "Sketch Book," and other productions, Undated (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Early to Bed, Undated (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Eastern Standard, Undated (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Eccentricities of a Nightingale, Undated (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Eden Court, Undated (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Educating Rita, Undated (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Edward II, Undated (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Effect of Gamma Rays on Man-in-the-Moon Marigolds, Undated (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Egg, Undated (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - 84 Charing Cross Road, Undated (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Einstein and the Polar Bear, Undated (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - El Grande de Coca-Cola, Undated (Box 11, Folder 34A)
  - Electra, Undated (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Eleemosynary, Undated (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Elephant Man, Undated (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Elizabeth the Queen, Undated (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Émigrés/Emigrants, Undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Enchanted, Undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Enclave, Undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - End as a Man, Undated (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Endgame, Undated (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Endicott and the Red Cross, Undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Enemy is Dead, Undated (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Enemy of the People, Undated (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Enter a Free Man, Undated (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Enter Laughing, Undated (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Entertainer, Undated (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Entertaining Mr. Sloane, Undated (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Epitaph for George Dillon, Undated (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Equus, Undated (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Escape Me Never, Undated (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Ethan Frome, Undated (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Evening[s] With…(Includes Bea Lillie, Nichols and May, Richard Nixon, Yves Montand), Undated (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Evening's Frost, Undated (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Every Good Boy Deserves Favor, Undated (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Everything in the Garden, Undated (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Eubie, Undated (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Eve of St. Mark, Undated (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Evita, Undated (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Execution of Justice, Undated (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Exercise, Undated (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Extremities, Undated (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - F, Undated (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - F, 1920s (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - F, 1930s (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - F, 1940s (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - F, 1950s (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - F (file 1 of 2), 1960s (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - F (file 2 of 2), 1960s (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - F, 1970s (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - F (file 1 of 2), 1980s (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - F (file 2 of 2), 1980s (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - F (file 1 of 2), 1990s (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - F (file 2 of 2), 1990s (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - F, 2000s (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Face of a Hero, Undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Fade Out-Fade In, Undated (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Fair Game, Undated (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Fallen Angels, Undated (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Falsettos, Falsettoland, Undated (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Fame. The Musical, Undated (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Family Business, Undated (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Family Portrait, Undated (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Fanny, Undated (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Fantasticks, Undated (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Far Country, Undated (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Farmer Takes a Wife, Undated (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Fashion, Undated (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Fatal Weakness, Undated (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Father, Undated (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Father's Day, Undated (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Feathertop, Undated (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Fences, Undated (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Festival, Undated (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Few Good Men, Undated (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Fiddler on the Roof, Undated (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Fifth of July, Undated (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Fifth Season, Undated (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Fifty Million Frenchmen, Undated (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Finian's Rainbow, Undated (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Finishing Touches, Undated (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Fiorello, Undated (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Firebugs, Undated (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Fires in the Mirror: Crown Heights, Brooklyn and Other Identities, Undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - First, Undated (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - First Lady, Undated (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - First Legion, Undated (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - First Monday in October, Undated (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Five Evenings, Undated (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Five Finger Exercise, Undated (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Five O'Clock Girl, Undated (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Flat Rock Playhouse, Undated (Box 14, Folder 12A)
  - Flea in Her Ear, Undated (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Flint, Undated (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Flora the Red Menace, Undated (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Flower Drum Song, Undated (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Flowering Peach, Undated (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - FOB, Undated (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Follies, Undated (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Follow the Girls, Undated (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Food Chain, Undated (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Fool for Love, Undated (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Fool Moon, Undated (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Fools, Undated (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - For Colored Girls who have Considered Suicide when the Rainbow is Enuf, Undated (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - For Love or Money, Undated (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Forbidden Broadway, Undated (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Foreigner, Undated (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Forever Plaid, Undated (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Forever Yours, Marie-Lou, Undated (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Fortune and Men's Eyes, Undated (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Forty Carats, Undated (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - 42nd Street, Undated (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Four Dogs and a Bone, Undated (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Four on a Garden, Undated (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Fourposter, Undated (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Foxfire, Undated (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Foxy, Undated (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Frankie and Johnny in the Clair de Lune, Undated (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - From the Mississippi Delta, Undated (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Front Page, Undated (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - Fugue in a Nursery, Undated (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - Full Gallop, Undated (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - Funny Face, Undated (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - Funny Girl, Undated (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - Funny Thing Happened on the Way to the Forum, Undated (Box 14, Folder 46)
  - Funnyhouse of a Negro, Undated (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - Futz, Undated (Box 14, Folder 48)
  - G, Undated (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - G, 1910s (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - G, 1920s (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - G, 1930s (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - G, 1940s (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - G (file 1 of 2), 1950s (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - G (file 2 of 2), 1950s (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - G (file 1 of 2), 1960s (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - G (file 2 of 2), 1960s (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - G (file 1 of 2), 1970s (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - G (file 2 of 2), 1970s (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - G (file 1 of 2), 1980s (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - G (file 2 of 2), 1980s (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - G, 1990s (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - G, 2000s (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Galileo, Undated (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Gang's All Here, Undated (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Gantry, Undated (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Gardenia, Undated (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Garrick Gaieties, Undated (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Gay Divorcé, Undated (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Gay Life, Undated (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Gazebo, Undated (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Gemini, Undated (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Generation, Undated (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Gentlemen Prefer Blondes, Undated (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Geniuses, Undated (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - George M, Undated (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - George Washington Slept Here, Undated (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - George White's Scandals, Undated (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Getting Out, Undated (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - GeVa Theatre, Undated (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Ghost Train, Undated (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Ghostman, Undated (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Ghosts, Undated (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Gideon, Undated (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Gift(s) of the Magi, Undated (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Gig, Undated (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Gigi, Undated (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Gilbert and Sullivan Company, Undated (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Gin Game, Undated (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Gingerbread Lady, Undated (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Girl Could Get Lucky, Undated (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Girl Crazy, Undated (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Girl's Guide to Chaos, Undated (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Give My Regards to Broadway, Undated (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Glass Menagerie, Undated (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Glengarry Glen Ross, Undated (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Glorious Morning, Undated (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Goblin Market, Undated (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - God of Vengeance, Undated (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Godspell, Undated (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Going Up, Undated (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Golden Age, Undated (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Golden Apple, Undated (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Golden Boy, Undated (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Golden Rainbow, Undated (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Goldilocks, Undated (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Golem, Undated (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - Gondoliers, Undated (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - Good, Undated (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - Good Doctor, Undated (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - Good Evening, Undated (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Good Housekeeping, Undated (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Good News, Undated (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Goodbye Girl, Undated (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Goodbye, My Fancy, Undated (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Goodbye People, Undated (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Goodnight Desdemona (Good Morning Juliet), Undated (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Goodnight Grandma, Undated (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Goodnight Mrs. Puffin, Undated (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Goodtime Charley, Undated (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - G.R. Point, Undated (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Grand Duke, Undated (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Grand Hotel, Undated (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Grand Tour, Undated (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Grapes of Wrath, Undated (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Grass Harp, Undated (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Grave Undertaking, Undated (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Grease, Undated (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Great Big Doorstep, Undated (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Great God Brown, Undated (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Great Lakes Shakespeare Festival, Undated (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Great Macdaddy, Undated (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Great Sebastians, Undated (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Great Waltz, Undated (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Great White Hope, Undated (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Greater Tuna, Undated (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Green Bay Tree, Undated (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Green Grow the Lilacs, Undated (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Green Pastures, Undated (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Greenwich Village Follies, Undated (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Greenwillow, Undated (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Greetings, Undated (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Grind, Undated (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Groucho, Groucho, A Life in Review, Undated (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Grown Ups, Undated (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Guardsman, Undated (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Guilty, Undated (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Guys and Dolls, Undated (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Gypsy, Undated (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - H, Undated (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - H, 1915 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - H, 1920s (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - H, 1930s (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - H (file 1 of 2), 1940s (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - H (file 2 of 2), 1940s (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - H (file 1 of 2), 1950s (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - H (file 2 of 2), 1950s (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - H (file 1 of 3), 1960s (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - H (file 2 of 3), 1960s (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - H (file 3 of 3), 1960s (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - H (file 1 of 2), 1970s (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - H (file 2 of 2), 1970s (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - H (file 1 of 3), 1980s (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - H (file 2 of 3), 1980s (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - H (file 3 of 3), 1980s (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - H (file 1 of 2), 1990s (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - H (file 2 of 2), 1990s (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - H, 2000s (Box 19, Folder 3A)
  - Habeas Corpus, Undated (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Hadrian VII, Undated (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Haggadah, A Passover Cantata, Undated (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Hair, Undated (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Half a Sixpence, Undated (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Hallelujah, Baby!, Undated (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Hamlet, Undated (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Happy as Larry, Undated (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Happy Birthday, Wanda June, Undated (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Happy Days, Undated (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Happy End, Undated (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Happy Hunting, Undated (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Happy Time, Undated (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Harold and Maude, Undated (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Harrigan and Hart, Undated (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Harvey, Undated (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Hasty Heart, Undated (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Hatful of Rain, Undated (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Having Our Say, Undated (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Hay Fever, Undated (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - He Who Gets Slapped, Undated (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Heartbeats, Undated (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Heartbreak House, Undated (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Hedda Gabler, Undated (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Heidi Chronicles, Undated (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Heiress, Undated (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Hello and Goodbye, Undated (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Hello Dolly, Undated (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Hello Muddah, Hello Faddah!, Undated (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Hellzapoppin, Undated (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Henry IV, Undated (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Henry V, Undated (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Henry VI, Undated (Box 20, Folder 3A)
  - Henry VIII, Undated (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Henry, Sweet Henry, Undated (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Her Cardboard Lover, Undated (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Here Come the Clowns, Undated (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Here's Love, Undated (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Hi-Hat Hattie, Undated (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Hide and Seek, Undated (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Hidden Horizon, Undated (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - High Button Shoes, Undated (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - High Kickers, Undated (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - High Spirits, Undated (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Him, Undated (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - History of the American Film, Undated (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Hit the Deck, Undated (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - H.M.S. Pinafore, Undated (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Hobson's Choice, Undated (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Hogan's Goat, Undated (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Hole in the Head, Undated (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Holiday, Undated (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Holiday Memories, Undated (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Hollow, Undated (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Hollow Crown, Undated (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Holy Ghosts, Undated (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Home, Undated (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Home of the Brave, Undated (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Homecoming, Undated (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Hooters, Undated (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Hosanna, Undated (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Hostage, Undated (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Hot Grog, Undated (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Hot L Baltimore, Undated (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Hot Mikado, Undated (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Hotel Paradiso, Undated (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Hothouse, Undated (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - House, Undated (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - House of Bernarda Alba, Undated (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - House of Blue Leaves, Undated (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - House of Flowers, Undated (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - How I Got That Story, Undated (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - How Now, Dow Jones, Undated (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - How the Other Half Loves, Undated (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - How to Succeed in Business Without Really Trying, Undated (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - Hudson Valley Shakespeare Festival, Undated (Box 20, Folder 46)
  - Human Comedy, Undated (Box 20, Folder 47)
  - Hunchback of Notre Dame, Undated (Box 20, Folder 48)
  - Hurlyburly, Undated (Box 20, Folder 49)
  - I, Undated (Box 20, Folder 50)
  - I, 1920s (Box 20, Folder 51)
  - I, 1930s (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - I, 1940s (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - I, 1950s (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - I (file 1 of 2), 1960s (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - I (file 2 of 2), 1960s (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - I (file 1 of 2), 1970s (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - I (file 2 of 2), 1970s (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - I (file 1 of 2), 1980s (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - I (file 2 of 2), 1980s (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - I, 1990s (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - I, 2000s (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - I Am A Camera, Undated (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - I Can Get It For You Wholesale, Undated (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - I Do! I Do!, Undated (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - I Hate Hamlet, Undated (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - I Have A Dream, Undated (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - I Knock at the Door, Undated (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - I Love My Wife, Undated (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - I Never Sang for My Father, Undated (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - I Remember Mama, Undated (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - I Won't Dance, Undated (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Iceman Cometh, Undated (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Ideal Husband, Undated (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Idiot's Delight, Undated (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Illusion, Undated (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Illya Darling, Undated (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - I'm Getting My Act Together And Taking It On The Road, Undated (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - I'm Not Rappaport, Undated (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Imaged, Undated (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Imaginary Invalid, Undated (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Immigrant, Undated (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Immoralist, Undated (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Importance of Being Earnest, Undated (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Impossible Years, Undated (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - In Praise of Love, Undated (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - In the Belly of the Beast, Undated (Box 22, Folder 6)